[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these statements, related to the effects of eating turkey, is true?", "correct_answer": "None of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Turkey slows your metabolic rate which makes you drowsy", "A turkey makes you sleepy as it contains the natural sedative L-tryptophan", "Increased blood flow to the gastrointestinal tract makes one drowsy"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The traditional Czech farmhouse hard cheese, made in Karlovy Vary, is known by what name?", "correct_answer": "Abertam", "incorrect_answers": ["Goutu", "Ambert", "Brie"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In which part of the human body are Sharpeys fibers found?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Skull", "Bones", "Teeth"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "12 squared is 24.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following is not regarded as one of the errors in the Back to the Future movies?", "correct_answer": "The clock in the McFly livingroom", "incorrect_answers": ["Martys pocket flap in Georges yard", "The last line of the letter to Doc warning him of his murder", "Pronunciation of gigawatts"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where does Charlie Chaplins character the Little Tramp work in the 1936 movie Modern Times?", "correct_answer": "In a factory", "incorrect_answers": ["In a hotel", "In a television studio", "On a construction site"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which movie, set in the small town of Endora, Iowa, contains these words: Say thank you, Gilbert. Say thank you.?", "correct_answer": "Whats Eating Gilbert Grape", "incorrect_answers": ["Pirates of the Carribbean", "The Window", "Basketball Diaries"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Why did the inventor of bubble gum make it pink?", "correct_answer": "It was the only color he had left", "incorrect_answers": ["He made it pink for his daughter", "It was his favorite color", "Pink reminded him of his mother"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "At the movies end, who falls off the altar stone of the Lost City of Atlantis into a tree?", "correct_answer": "Alec (Alexander) McEwen", "incorrect_answers": ["Carla Goetaborg", "Guide Hans Belke", "Oliver S. Lindenbrook"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What movie earned Sean Penn his first Academy Award for Best Actor?", "correct_answer": "Mystic River", "incorrect_answers": ["Dead Man Walking", "Sweet and Lowdown", "I Am Sam"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The state drink of this US state is milk, its state bird is the Western Meadowlark, its state flower is the Wild Prairie Rose, and its state slogan is Legendary.", "correct_answer": "North Dakota", "incorrect_answers": ["South Dakota", "North Carolina", "South Carolina"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What Gorilla is the largest primate on the planet?", "correct_answer": "Eastern Lowland Gorilla", "incorrect_answers": ["Mountain Gorilla", "Western Lowland Gorilla", "Cross River Gorilla"]}]